T: Annie? Annie, honey, are you here?
An: Terry?
T: Yeah Annie, it’s me.
T: Are you okay?
An: They’re coming, Terry…
An: All of those monsters…
An: They’re coming here.
T: I know Annie.
T: Are you going to be okay?
An: I keep hearing them in my sleep,
An: Especially the bug ones.
T: The flying ones?
An: No, the little ones. The ones that skitter around and spit acid.
T: Yeah, they’re awful.
T: But that’s never bugged you before.
T: What’s different now?
An: Just…
An: All the death.
An: On our side.
An: On theirs.
T: You’re sick of it?
An: No, it’s more than that.
An: I keep seeing them everywhere inside the base.
An: Do you remember last night when I jumped out of bed?
T: Yeah, you were digging through your dresser.
T: You’d said you had a nightmare.
An: It wasn’t a nightmare. I couldn’t sleep.
An: I was staring at the closet, blood pumping.
An: I kept seeing shadows peaking out from behind the door. I could hear them, buzzing, stomping and oozing. 
An: All the monsters we’ve seen so far. I kept seeing them behind the door.
T: Annie…
An: I knew it wasn’t real, but I couldn’t stop staring.
An: And then I thought I saw one of those… blob monster things.
An: I saw it seep through the door.
An: I could have sworn it was real.
An: I reached to my side to grab my pistol, but I wasn’t wearing my holster.
T: You were in bed, sweetie.
An: But I was so scared I couldn’t find it.
An: I just wanted to fill it full of lead.
An: I was shaking.
T: Is that why you’re here now?
An: I just…
An: I needed to be away from everything.
T: Okay.
T: Well I’m here now.
T: And I’m not going to leave you-
An: No, no, I need some time alone right now.
T: Annie-
An: Go away Terry.
An: Please.
An: I don’t want you to see me like this.
T: I-
T: …
T: Okay. Let me know if you need anything.
An: …
T: Have you talked to the doctor yet about this?
T: Even the chaplain could help-
An: Leave. Me. Alone. 
An: Terry.
T: …
T: Okay.
