D: You’re probably wondering why I gathered you all here today.
A: …
S: …
D: Oh come on. You could at least try to guess.
A: I was going to point out that everyone here is both a girl and unattached, but Taliyah and Jai are missing.
D: Close! I mean, I tried getting Tali here… 
D: … But she declined.
D: Aggressively.
S: And Jai?
D: …
D: …
D: …
A: Uh… Devi?
D: Sorry, just remembering something. 
D: I think Jai would benefit from some alone time right now.
S: So what, you gathered us here to talk about boys? 
S: Because, to be honest, that sounds really stupid.
D: What? God no. 
D: I just wanted to hide from responsibility, and I figured that this was a great way to do it!
D: So, tell me about yourselves. You both went to the same school, right?
D: What was that like?
S: It was a good time. It was a pretty great school.
A: Uh-huh. 
A: Sabrina and I didn’t really talk much back then.
S: But we’re good friends now!
D: So, what brought you guys to military life?
A: I uh… Needed a distraction. Something to keep me busy.
S: I spent my whole life with my family controlling everything. I just wanted an escape, you known.
S: Plus Ashe was here, so I figured… Why not?
A: Huh. I didn’t think…
S: So Devi, why are you here?
D: Kind of the same really. Just getting away from my mistakes.
D: Look, it’s been kind of stressful lately.
D: Why don’t I pull a favours, and get us the rest of the day off.
D: I can find some people to cover for us.
A: Uh…
S: Is that responsible?
D: Pfft, who cares. I’ll make sure nothing bad will happen.
D: Most of our days are conflict. We need the break.
A: Alright, cool.
S: I guess I could use the break.
D: Perfect! Give me 30 minutes to set everything up.
[Devi walks away from the group]
D: Man, poor Sabrina. Ashe has no idea she’s interested.
D: Ah, young love…
