D: Alright, so I think if we can put in a order for a few M63’s, that’ll help keep our damage output but lower the load on our guys.
D: Hopefully that means we can actually outrun an ultra if they get past the other squads.
L: Uh, Devi? If I’m reading these reports right, M63’s are like… New. Really New. I don’t think that we can just ship them here.
L: I mean, Roy’s mercs could probably buy a couple. 
L: But despite how friendly the guy is, I doubt he’ll just give us a few.
D: You’re probably right… 
D: Alright, I know a few guys. I’ll pull a few favours.
L: Like… Military guys?
D: Just some friends I know, don’t worry about it!
L: …
L: What did you say you did before the military?
D: Oh you know, this and that. 
D: I did a lot of work as a debt collector, with Jai.
L: Speaking of Jai… 
L: This is a meeting for Machine Gunners. Why is she here?
J: Do you have a problem with that?
L: NO! I mean… Uh. Of course not.
J: Look, if you ha-
D: Easy, relax Jai. He didn’t mean anything by it.
J: …
J: Alright. If you say so.
J: … I’m calm.
D: I know you are.
D: Hey Larry, can you go to the quartermaster and make sure we are ordering enough rounds?
L: Uh. Yeah. Sure. Right away.
J: ...
D: *sigh* That man has such a crush on me.
J: Is he a problem for you?
D: No, no. Nothing like that.
D: I just don’t really know what to do with him…
D: Eh, it’s not your problem, I’ll figure it out later.
D: Besides, we still have monsters to kill.
