G: Yes?
G: Taliyah, you didnt come here to start anything again, did you?
T: No Quartermaster Géoff, I did not.
T: I am here in a formal capacity, per your request.
T: Now, is there a reason why my troops haven’t received their requested equipment yet?
G: Because I had to cancel their order. 
T: Oh?
T: Why?
G: Because of a report one of the armoury guards wrote.
G: Apparently, soldiers from your garrison tried to forcibly enter the armory,
G: And attempted to steal several crates of high-calibre ammunition.
T: Did they now?
G: Did you have anything to do with that?
T: I did not.
T: But I think my soldiers are right in wanting to be well prepared.
T: And I see no reason to cripple their combat potential.
G: That isn’t your call.
G: From now on you are to come directly to me for these things.
G: Do you understand?
T: You’re asking me to trust your judgement?
G: It doesn’t matter whether you trust me.
G: This is my responsibility,
G: And you will respect my authority as Quartermaster.
T: …
T: Do you remember Miriam Korlokov, Géoff?
G: Who?
T: I thought you wouldn’t know her.
T: It makes sense.
T: She was one of the NCO’s in my company,
T: during our campaign on Gratham Ridge.
G: …
T: You see, Miriam was the kind of girl who held her drink tightly with both hands when she drank,
T: Like she was afraid she would drop it at any moment.
T: And she had those lofty, innocently curious eyes.
T: I used to make fun of her because the men in my company asked her out all the time.
T: She was so shy and adorable.
T: Smart as a whip too,
T: I always wondered what the hell she was doing in a fighting corp.
G: Get to your point, Taliyah?
T: She died at Gratham Ridge.
T: She died trying to cover the flank that your troops left open when you retreated.
T: And in doing that, she took the brunt of an explosion from an anti-tank shell.
T: I didn’t see it at the time, but I saw her afterwards.
T: Her body was crumpled and flat,
T: Bent backwards and wrapped around a boulder, 
T: like she had been printed onto it.
T: Her blood sprayed out from the top of her head.
T: And her eyes…
T: Well,
T: Have you ever seen one of those dogs with a detached eye?
T: Where one eye is looking at you, but the other is jerked out in some god awful direction.
T: She was like that.
T: With one eye looking up towards the sky and the other staring right at me.
T: I still see her corpse staring at me.
T: Every morning when I look at the clock.
T: Every time I go jogging near the mountains.
T: Every day.
T: You did that to me, Géoff.
T: You did that to her.
T: You might think that you have the right to make whatever call you want,
T: But my people trust me to have their best interests in mind,
T: And I’m not giving you another chance to let me down,
T: Or to let anyone else die like Miriam.
T: Do you understand me?
G: …
G: What happened on Gratham Ridge wasn’t my fault.
G: If I hadn’t retreated my men would have died.
T: We could have stood a chance together.
G: We couldn’t have! 
G: There was no way,
G: There were too many of them.
G: I made a call and I stand by it.
T: …
T: Maybe you’re right.
T: Maybe we couldn’t have won.
T: But your call left my people alone to take them on ourselves.
T: And our potential win became an absolute slaughter.
T: That was your fault.
T: Now are you going to get my men their munitions or not?
G: Damn it Woman, there aren’t any extra munitions,
G: Everyone gets an equal budget of supplies and we all need to stay within that budget,
G: That is how logistics works.
T: I don’t care how you think logistics work.
T: Figure out how my units can operate dependently from you or I’ll be coming back tomorrow.
T: Goodbye, Géoff.
G: …
G: Damn that woman.
