R: Heya buddy. Come here often?
Y: Ah, the buffoon himself. 
R: Why does everyone start with name calling? It hurts, man.
Y: It is because you and your troops treat combat as a game.
Y: You don’t treat death with respect.
Y: And you all lack professionalism.
R: Huh. That homesick, huh?
Y: And you can’t even take this conversation seriously.
R: Relax, sheesh. If you keep this up you’ll have more wrinkles than Murphy.
Y: If you keep up your attitude, you’ll get yourself and others killed.
R: I’ve made it this far! Whadd’ya call that?
Y: Blind luck. 
R: Ouch. You’re definitely from Canuckistan alright. Why’d you quit?
Y: As if you would understand, mercenary. 
Y: Go back to preparing for your games.
Y: I need to prepare for the coming battle.
R: Okay buddy. I just needed to know if I can trust you to watch my back.
Y: …
Y: Grudgingly. 
R: Then everything’s all good. See you at the battlefield!