An: Well well well, how is my brother in law doing?
L: I wish I could say great, but your husband managed to hide all my clothes…
L: Right before I was supposed to give a speech to my squad.
T: Hey, you have no proof that it was me.
L: Riiiight. Sure. It’s just a coincidence that this happened right after I painted all your equipment pink.
An: You two are adorable.
L: I like to think I’m pretty cool myself. I mean, look at my blue hair. 
L: You know, if you ever get bored of my lame older brother.
L: I’m still single.
An: Ha! I’ll think about it.
An: But I don’t even think you could keep up with me.
An: I mean, you machine gunners always seem to keep in the back.
T: Besides Larry. What’s the current score? 7 to 1?
L: No! It’s only 7 to 4.
L: ….
L: Damn it.
An: Ouch...
T: Come on Larry! I know you can pull better pranks than this. 
T: What’s the matter, military life dull your senses?
L:  Okay brother. You asked for it. 
L: Just remember whatever happens next, you deserve it.
An: You know, one of these days you guys should get to meet MY family.  